hustlercontent.com 2010-06-25

# Privacy Statement for LFP, Inc

**LFP Internet Group, LLC. ("LFP")** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the websites operated by us.

**IP Addresses:** when visitors access our websites, we automatically capture the IP address of the source computer, the referring site and the destination site. We use this information to control access to our websites, and to optimize the presentation of our websites. IP addresses may also be used to help identify users and to gather broad demographic information. We also capture data on which pages have been accessed by visitors, and the frequency with which they are accessed.This information is used to understand our visitors’ preferences and to balance the load on our servers.

**Cookies:** "Cookies" are small files of data that reside on visitors’ computers. Cookies allow us to recognize visitors, customize their experience, and offer efficiencies related to login and access. We set a "Session Cookie" upon visitor login to enable them to access multiple domains without having to re-enter login information. Once a user closes their browser, Session Cookies become inactive. We may also set longer-lasting cookies to make login procedures more efficient for returning members. These may contain email addresses or usernames which are encrypted so they can be interpreted only by LFP. From time to time we may share cookie information with third-party partners with whom we have an official relationship. This is done to make the establishment of new accounts more efficient, and to facilitate special offers. Most browsers have settings that enable users to disable cookies on their machines. If cookies are disabled, certain website services or functionality may not function properly.

**Third-Party Websites:** LFP websites often contain links to websites operated by other companies that are not controlled by LFP. LFP therefore has no responsibility or liability for the policies, activities or content of these sites. Nonetheless, we seek to provide our visitors with a positive experience, so we welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Public Forums:** websites operated by LFP may contain chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. LFP prohibits the posting of illegal or defamatory content in its chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups, and reserves the right to remove any user-posted content at LFP’s sole discretion. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when disclosing personal information.

**Financial Information:** financial information, such as a credit card number or bank account number, is captured when users place an order or make a purchase. Financial information is used to check the purchaser’s qualifications and to process payment(s) for products and services ordered. Financial data is only captured on web pages that reside on secure servers. Transmission of financial data over the Internet is always fully encrypted. Storage of financial information is only handled by third-party PCI-compliant payment processors. After a transaction, no financial data resides on LFP servers.  Financial information is never shared with any parties other than the financial institutions directly involved in processing the transaction.

**Personal Information:** personal information such as a person’s first name, last name or billing address, is captured when a user places an order or makes a purchase. This information is used to check the purchaser’s qualifications and to process payment(s) for products and services ordered. This information is also used for customer support purposes. We may disclose personal information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process. We may also disclose personal information in the course of investigating suspected fraud or other illegal activity. Outside of the aforementioned legal processes, personal information is never shared with any parties other than the financial institutions directly involved in processing the transaction.

**Customer Information:** customer information such as a username, password or email address can be captured when a customer registers on a website, places an order, subscribes to a newsletter, responds to a survey, or otherwise enters information into a form on one of our websites. Customer information is primarily used to manage access to our websites and to communicate with customers when necessary about membership, product, billing or other support-related concerns. We may retain correspondence such as e-mails or faxes for the purpose of customer support reference and improvement. Customer information may also be used to convey company news, administer a contest, conduct a survey, communicate a special offer from a preferred partner, or promote internal programs. All promotional emails contain an easy and automated way to unsubscribe from receiving future emails. Alternatively, recipients can also unsubscribe from receiving future emails by sending a request to [unsubscribe@hustleremail.com](mailto:unsubscribe@hustleremail.com).

**Consent:** by accepting the Terms and Conditions during registration, website visitors expressly consent to the use and disclosure of personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

**Questions:** If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may email us at [support@hustler.com](mailto:support@hustler.com), or send a letter to: 

LFP Internet Group, LLC  
8484 Wilshire Blvd Suite #900  
Beverly Hills, CA 90211  
USA

**Version:** LFP reserves the right to update its privacy policy at its own discretion. Upon making changes to our privacy policy, we will publish a new "last modified" date below.

This policy was last modified on November 4, 2009.
